A Guide to the Association of National Investigators Collection, 1925-1931
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
Association of National Investigators Collection, 1925-1931
The Edgar Cayce Foundation, Virginia Beach, Virginia
Coll. 7
0.9 Linear Feet
Blumenthal, Morton; Cayce, Edgar; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Sugrue, Thomas
Scope and Contents
This collection includes booklets, brochures, a charter, correspondence, lectures, financial records, inventories, membership applications, patient charts recording the medical history and treatments of patients admitted to the Cayce Hospital, postcards, and reports documenting the activities of the Association of National Investigators. The collection also includes the original print run of The New-Tomorrow journal (edited by Thomas Sugrue and Hugh Lynn Cayce).
Arrangement
2 boxes arranged alphabetically.
Custodial History
The records in this collection were originally the property of the Association of National Investigators. After the A.N.I.'s dissolution, they became the personal property of Edgar Cayce. The Edgar Cayce Foundation possibly received the records at its creation in 1948.
Association of National Investigators
- Box 1
  - booklets, 1926-1929; Folder 1:1
  - booklet [Testimony], 1930; Folder 1:2
  - brochure [Cayce Hospital], 1928; Folder 1:3
  - charter, 1927; Folder 1:4
  - correspondence [dissolution], 1931; Folder 1:5
  - correspondence [patients], 1929-1930; Folder 1:6
  - dedication address [Cayce Hospital], 1928; Folder 1:7
  - financial records [Cayce Hospital], 1929; Folder 1:8
  - flyers [Cayce Hospital], 1928; Folder 1:9
  - inventory [Cayce Hospital], 1930; Folder 1:10
  - journal [The New To-Morrow], 1929-1930; Folder 1:11-1:13
  - lectures [Morton Blumenthal], 1928; Folder 1:14
  - logo, 1927; Folder 1:15
  - membership applications, 1927; Folder 1:16
  - patient charts [Cayce Hospital], 1929; Folder 1:17
  - postcards [Cayce Hospital], 1929; Folder 1:18
  - proxy voting forms, 1928-1929; Folder 1:19
- Box 2
  - reports, 1925-1930; Folder 2:1-2:6